http://www.medacademy.org/cookie-policy-us/

Skip to contentPrograms and CoursesCertificate ProgramsDental Assistant ProgramMedical Assistant ProgramMedical Assistant With Phlebotomy ProgramDiploma ProgramsLimited X-Ray Technician with MA Skills ProgramPsychiatric Technician ProgramVocational Nurse ProgramAssociate Degree ProgramsA.S. in Magnetic Resonance Imaging ProgramA.S. in Nursing ProgramA.S. in Physical Therapist Assistant ProgramA.O.S. in Radiologic Technology ProgramA.S. in Radiologic Technology ProgramA.O.S. in Ultrasound Technology ProgramA.S. in Vocational Nursing ProgramBachelor's Degree ProgramsB.S. in Diagnostic Medical Imaging ProgramB.S. in Nursing (BSN) ProgramRN to BSN ProgramContinuing Education CoursesCPR for Basic Life Support CourseIV Therapy and Blood Withdrawal CourseInternational CoursesInternational Nurse Graduate CoursesCampus LocationsOnline LearningConcord CampusFresno CampusModesto CampusSacramento CampusSan Mateo CampusVan Nuys CampusCorporate OfficeStudentsCatalog and AddendumCareer Services DepartmentForeign Transcript EvaluationsGeneral Admission RequirementsHoliday ScheduleReplacement Diploma RequestStudent FormsStudent Services DepartmentTranscript RequestVeterans BenefitsFinancialCost of AttendanceFinancial AidMake an Online PaymentNet Price CalculatorResourcesBrochuresCareer Training VideosCOVID-19 Resources and FAQsDistance Education RequirementsEvent VideosHealthcare Career BlogNewsPoliciesRequired DisclosuresStudent TestimonialsAbout UsAccreditation and ApprovalClinical RotationsFaculty and StaffFrom the Desk of the CEOHire a Gurnick GraduateMission StatementWhy Students Choose GurnickWork at GurnickStudent LoginGurnick EdgeGurnick Online (Moodle)Student PortalADB/Complio Immunization Tracking Read the Latest COVID-19 UpdatesEnroll Now & Take Classes From Home Apply Now Take a Virtual TourCookie Policy (US)This page was last changed on September 21, 2020, last checked on September 21, 2020, and applies to United States citizens.1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.gurnick.edu (hereinafter: “the website”), uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience, all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged in. In the document below, we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small, simple file sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or the relevant third parties’ servers during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website used to monitor traffic on a website. Various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settings FunctionalMarketing You can also disable cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work correctly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to enter the same information when visiting our website repeatedly, and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Advertising cookiesOn this website, we use advertising cookies, enabling us to gain insights into the campaign results. This happens based on a profile we create based on your behavior on https://www.gurnick.edu. As a website visitor, you are linked to a unique ID with these cookies but will not profile your behavior and interests to serve personalized ads.You can object to the tracking by these cookies by clicking the “Revoke cookie consent” button.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website, we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Pinterest to promote webpages (e.g. “like,” “pin”) or share (e.g., “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Pinterest. These buttons work using code coming from Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Pinterest themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information so that a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data, which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Pinterest are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesWooCommerceWe use WooCommerce for webshop management. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionFunctional  wc_cart_hash_*sessionStore items in shopping cartwoocommerce_items_in_cartsessionStore items in shopping cartwoocommerce_cart_hashOne dayStore items in shopping cartwp_woocommerce_session_*sessionStore performed actions on the websitewc_fragments_*persistent wc_cart_createdsessionStore performed actions on the websiteSharingThis data is not shared with third parties.WP-OptimizeRead moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  tablesorter-savesort  SharingThis data is not shared with third parties.HotjarWe use Hotjar for heat maps and screen recordings. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionStatistics  _hjid1 yearStore a unique user IDSharingFor more information, please read the Hotjar Privacy Statement.Google AnalyticsWe use Google Analytics for website statistics. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionStatistics (anonymous)  _ga2 yearsCount and track pageviews_gid1 dayCount and track pageviewsSharingFor more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.FacebookWe use Facebook for the display of recent social posts or social share buttons. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  _fbp  _fbc  _js_datr  actppresence  fbm*  xs  wd  fr  act  datr  c_user  csm  sb  presence  *_fbm_  SharingFor more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.Google Tag ManagerWe use Google Tag Manager for website statistics. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  calltrk_session_id1 year Marketing/Tracking  _gat_gtag_UA_*_11 hourStore and track conversionsSharingThis data is not shared with third parties.AutomatticWe use Automattic for website development. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionStatistics  tk_aisessionStore a unique user IDSharingFor more information, please read the Automattic Privacy Statement.MatomoWe use Matomo for website statistics. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionStatistics (anonymous)  _pk_ref*6 monthsStore referrer ID’s_pk_id*13 monthsStore a unique user ID_pk_ref*6 monthsStore referrer ID’s_pk_id*13 monthsStore a unique user IDSharingThis data is not shared with third parties.WistiaWe use Wistia for video display. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  wistia  Statistics  wistia-video-progress-*persistentStore if the user has seen embedded contentSharingFor more information, please read the Wistia Privacy Statement.TwitterWe use Twitter for the display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  local_storage_support_test  metrics_token  SharingFor more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Statement.LinkedInWe use LinkedIn for the display of recent social posts or social share buttons. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  bcookie  li-oatml  BizographicsOptOut  li_sugr  UserMatchHistory  linkedin_oauth_*  lidc  bscookie  X-LI-IDC  SharingFor more information, please read the LinkedIn Privacy Statement.Google FontsWe use Google Fonts for the display of web fonts. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  Google Fonts API  SharingFor more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.VimeoWe use Vimeo for video display. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  __utmt_player  vuid  SharingFor more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.MixpanelWe use Mixpanel for website statistics. Read moreNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  *_mixpanel  SharingFor more information, please read the Mixpanel Privacy Statement.MiscellaneousNameRetentionFunctionPurpose pending investigation  _hjAbsoluteSessionInProgress  ub-emb-*  __mp_opt_in_out_5d545622e3a040aca63f2089b0e6cae7  ub-emb-id  _hjIncludedInPageviewSample  calltrk_landing  calltrk_referrer  ubvs  ubvt  theme-ui-color-mode  loglevel  expandedItems  skyVergeNoticeCounts  undefined  SharingThis data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights concerning personal data You have the following rights concerning your data:you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;you may object to the processing;you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the information we process about you;you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant or to ask to restrict the data’s processing.To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you complain about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you. 9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change your internet browser’s settings so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. Please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser for more information about these options.10. Selling data to third partiesWe do not sell data to third parties11. Contact detailsFor questions or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Gurnick Academy of Medical Arts, LLC. 2121 South El Camino Real, Building C-200, San Mateo, CA 94403 United States Website: https://www.gurnick.edu Email: marketing@gurnick.edu Phone number: 650-685-6616This Cookie Policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on September 21, 2020 © Copyright 2020 Gurnick Academy Disclosures Privacy Policy Sitemap CCPA CARES Act Reports Is Healthcare Career Training Right for You? Take the Free Quiz!
